https://asdlighting.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyASD Lighting PLC privacy policy
Your privacy is critically important to us.ASD Lighting PLC is located at:ASD Lighting PLC, Mangham Road, Barbot Hall Industrial Estate, S61 4RJIt is ASD Lighting PLC’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. This Privacy Policy applies to https://asdlighting.com (hereinafter, “us”, “we”, or “asdlighting.com”). We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personally identifiable information you may provide us through the Website. We have adopted this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) to explain what information may be collected on our Website, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties. This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect through the Website and does not apply to our collection of information from other sources.This Privacy Policy, together with the Terms and conditions posted on our Website, set forth the general rules and policies governing your use of our Website. Depending on your activities when visiting our Website, you may be required to agree to additional terms and conditions.Website VisitorsLike most website operators, ASD Lighting PLC collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. ASD Lighting PLC’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how ASD Lighting PLC’s visitors use its website.ASD Lighting PLC also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for users downloading content. ASD Lighting PLC only discloses user IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.Gathering of Personally-Identifying InformationCertain visitors to ASD Lighting PLC’s websites choose to interact with ASD Lighting PLC in ways that require ASD Lighting PLC to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that ASD Lighting PLC gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who download media at asdlighting.com to provide a name, email address and their business details.SecurityThe security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.Links To External SitesOur Service may contain links to external sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy and terms and conditions of every site you visit.We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites, products or services.Aggregated StatisticsASD Lighting PLC may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. ASD Lighting PLC does not display this information publicly or provide it to others.CookiesTo enrich and perfect your online experience, ASD Lighting PLC uses “Cookies”, similar technologies and services provided by others to display personalized content, appropriate advertising and store your preferences on your computer.A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. ASD Lighting PLC uses cookies to help ASD Lighting PLC identify and track visitors, their usage of asdlighting.com, and their website access preferences. ASD Lighting PLC visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using ASD Lighting PLC’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of ASD Lighting PLC’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.By continuing to navigate our website without changing your cookie settings, you hereby acknowledge and agree to ASD Lighting PLC’s use of cookies.Privacy Policy ChangesAlthough most changes are likely to be minor, ASD Lighting PLC may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in ASD Lighting PLC’s sole discretion. ASD Lighting PLC encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
×
This field is required.
This field is required.
This field is required.
This field is required.
This field is required.
I agree to the terms set out in our Privacy Policy*
This field is required.
I would like to subscribe to ASD Lighting’s mailing list to be notified of new or updated products.
×
